[In My Prime]
[Episode 6]
Hello,
honey.
When are you coming back?
I can't fall asleep without you.
I...
Hello?
She hung up on me again.
Just find a way
to subtly let her know that
some of the help she's giving
is already putting
a strain
on you, on me,
and on everyone.
That will do.
You must be Aihua's mother!
And you are?
I'm from the Neighborhood Committee.
Your neighbors have complained about
a foul smell
that's always coming from your house.
I'm here to check.
Where is the foul smell?
Why can't I smell it?
You city people
are just too fussy.
I'm pickling some vegetables
in my own house.
What's wrong?
Does it have anything to do with you?
I can do whatever I want
at my own place.
Not even God could
tell me what to do!
You...
What kind of attitude is that?
In this math exam,
none of you did very well.
You need to review your mistakes later.
Cao Xin, first place,
129 points.
Thank you, sir.
Tian Zihao,
88 points.
There are only two
in our class who failed the exam.
Thank you, sir.
At least I've got a fellow classmate
who also failed this time.
Qi Shi,
89 points.
-Qi Shi?
Never thought
Qi Shi would be at the bottom with me.
What's wrong with you?
How did your grades drop so much?
I'm sorry, sir.
Wang Yuxin,
93 points.
Your homeroom teacher
came by today,
saying your grades
dropped greatly recently
because you spent
your spare time collecting
scrap cardboard with me.
I could tell it.
Your teacher
was implying that
I'm holding you back from your studies
and ruining your future.
Grandma,
I really want to focus on my studies.
I...
Mom,
did you have a fight with the staff from
the Neighborhood Committee?
What's wrong?
Our household got a complaint.
They said
they came to mediate this morning,
and you kicked them out.
Is that true?
In the end, they reported it
to the Health Bureau.
This matter has blown up.
I was simply pickling vegetables
in my own home.
Does the Health Bureau
even deal with this?
Mom,
p-please just dispose of
these pickled vegetables.
They said
the Health Bureau's staff
might come and fine us.
I did nothing wrong!
Why fine us?
How am I supposed to get by with all this?
Mom!
You're not in the countryside.
You can't just do things recklessly
a-as you did in the village.
Also, look,
you made Qinglian so mad
that she went back to her parents' house.
What a mess this is!
You all think
it's my fault, right?
I made Shi collect scrap cardboard
to make her work more diligently!
Who did I pickle vegetables for?
Was it for myself?
It was all for you guys!
After all is said and done,
you all blame me.
Are you despising me?
As a mother,
I'm doing everything just for you,
and you still complain, huh?
Fine.
You three are a family,
and I'm the only outsider.
Since you're all upset about me,
I won't stay here any longer
as a nuisance.
Grandma,
that's not what we meant.
Yeah, Mom,
Please don't be mad.
Grandma.
Mom.
-Mom...
-Grandma.
Mom...
Calm down, please.
If you're really going to leave,
have a meal first,
and I'll take you to the station!
Go see your grandma off.
That's your mom. Why don't you go?
My mom left.
So I have to go pick up your mom.
Go ahead.
Grandma, wait for me!
Grandpa,
out of 150 points,
90 is a passing grade,
and she scored exactly 89,
right on the edge of passing.
What does that mean?
Xin.
Qi Shi
got not a point more or a point less,
just enough to fail.
What does this mean?
She knows all the correct answers!
And it just perfectly triggered
her grandma's guilt.
I knew
someone could deal with this old madam.
I can finally go home.
Grandma,
you seem quite happy.
I'm going back to my own home.
How could I not be happy?
Over the past few days at your place,
I could neither eat well
nor sleep well,
and nothing went my way.
There were endless things
springing up every day
to deal with and worry about.
I've been dog-tired.
Well,
then why didn't you go back earlier?
I wanted to leave a long time ago.
But seeing how you guys
seem to need me for everything,
I couldn't bring myself
to leave you behind.
So in your eyes,
we are a big burden.
You are burdens.
But I am
willing to carry you.
You're
all troublemakers.
But what can I do? I'm a mother.
Alright.
Go back now.
G-Grandma.
I...
I want to confess something to you.
Anything else?
I did poorly on this exam
on purpose, actually.
I...
I knew we could make money
by collecting cardboard,
but it was really scorching hot
in the sun.
I didn't want to do it,
so I came up with this terrible idea.
You brat.
At my age,
I still got lectured
by your teacher for ages.
Do you have any idea
how worried I was about you?
You... You brat.
Why are you so disobedient?
Grandma, Grandma...
Don't be mad. Calm down.
If you get sick over this, we'll pay
for treatment.
It's not worth it.
Alright, alright.
Alright, enough.
Go back now.
I'm leaving.
Qi Shi,
listen to me
and take off your wig.
It's not good to always keep it on.
Also,
be more diligent.
Don't take after your mom.
Lazybones
don't have good luck.
I got it.
I'm leaving. You may go back.
Qi Shi, go back now.
Go back.
Bye, Grandma.
Go back, go back.
You may go back now.
Let me do it.
Honey, you've suffered.
Anyway,
through our joint efforts,
we finally talked my mom
into going back home.
Keep it there.
In the future,
our household
will still be yours to manage.
Alright.
Qi Shi, time to eat.
When I was at my parents' house
the past few days,
I also reflected
on myself seriously.
With your mom's bossy attitude
when she talks,
she's actually quite like me.
So from now on, I will
change my attitude at home.
Is this still my mom?
I fried an egg specifically for you.
No more pickles.
Let me do it. Let me.
Bossy people are
indeed not popular
with others.
Despite their good intentions,
others still won't appreciate it.
I don't want to be like your grandma.
I've decided that from now on,
I'll change,
be tolerant,
and be open-minded.
Aihua,
do you want me to fry an egg for you, too?
C-Can I have it?
[Art of Marriage]
Why did Mom start reading a book?
Don't underestimate your mom.
Your mom actually
finished junior high.
You know what?
Comparison makes a difference.
Your grandma's visit
made your mom fully realize
the wisdom of managing a household.
Look,
she's started to learn right away.
Your grandma's visit
was well worth it.
So do you think
our days
are going to get better?
Yes.
You know what?
From now on,
we can just enjoy our lives.
This water is a bit cold.
Add some more hot water for me.
Honey.
Could you cut two slices of ginger for me
to warm up?
Is this okay?
Yep.
Mom,
I want some fried mushrooms.
Put more cumin.
Mom!
I want to eat fried mushrooms right now.
Could you give me a foot massage?
I'm a bit tired from standing all day.
A foot massage?
I think you're asking for a beating!
You two are getting on my nerves,
huh?
You two can't live a day
without causing trouble,
can you?
You're making demands of me? How dare you?
And you!
Don't run away!
You think I'm a pushover
just because I haven't shown you
what I've got?
Where are you two going to hide?
Get down here!
How dare you two
walk all over me?
No food for you tomorrow!
Mom is so back.
This is your real mom.
Don't just eat meat.
Have some veggies
for balanced nutrition.
Thanks, Dad.
In my point of view,
you should eat
even more meat.
Otherwise,
how can you finish the huge pile
of homework
your dad has assigned you?
Dad,
after Old Madam Qi came,
Mrs. Huo has become
a whole different person.
She is friendly with everyone
and doesn't even dare to breathe heavily.
When my mom was alive,
did she also act that way before Grandma?
Your grandma passed away
even earlier than your mom.
They didn't have the time
or the chance to not get along.
These neighbors of ours
make a fuss
every day.
It's so chaotic,
isn't it?
Our home is much better.
Quiet and peaceful.
What?
Big guy, you didn't grow for nothing.
You actually know how to help now.
I will
wash my own clothes from now on.
Just leave it to me.
You're getting passionate
after a few compliments, huh?
What? Are you shy?
You know,
I've been washing your clothes
for as long as
you've been alive,
ever since
you were in diapers.
I was a little kid myself
and wasn't very tall.
I would take a small stool,
stand on it,
and keep scrubbing.
But I just couldn't scrub it off.
So for a long time,
you smelled sour.
You're so annoying!
What else could I do?
It's not your fault
you were born without a mom.
At least I had Mom around for 4 years.
I'd just get myself
to be half a mom to you.
But you were also a kid back then.
Who was there to be your mom?
I had Mrs. Huo.
Later...
But you've grown up now
and can take care of yourself.
I won't be able to be
like your mom for much longer.
Give them to me.
We agreed I'd do it myself.
Here's yours.
How are you going to live
on your own?
You don't even know how to fold clothes.
Fold these two sleeves back.
Like this, this...
See?
Done.
So easy.
Good students just have different brains.
Li Bo,
good luck with the game this afternoon.
Catch it.
So smelly.
Don't worry.
We won't lose.
Listen, you must
do your best for the Central League
this afternoon.
No worries.
You know how good I am.
Qi Shi.
Qi Shi!
Can I borrow your science paper?
-Okay.
-I didn't solve
the last major question.
Not bad, Cao Xin.
You even got this question right.
But
why did you score 20 points
less than Qi Shi?
I thought you
only missed the last major question.
When it comes to studying,
you need a role model
who's truly exceptional.
Check out my paper, girl.
It's the real deal.
You got 4 multiple-choice questions wrong?
Wait,
even I got this question right!
What's wrong with you?
I felt drowsy during the exam.
I wasn't sober when doing
those questions.
You really can make things up.
What do you mean?
You woke up as you did more questions?
Can't I?
You can, you can.
I wonder who was kicking himself
for being 20 points away
from beating me in the monthly exam.
You've worked on
your mistake notebook so hard, right?
Is it useful?
You'll be sleepy again next time.
No,
you'll have a new excuse next time.
Here.
Feel free to ask me if you
have any questions.
I definitely won't feel drowsy
explaining questions to you.
It's been so many years.
Why are they still bickering?
It's not your first time
being in the same class as them.
They've been competing
since elementary school
all the way until now.
Neither will yield to the other.
Let me see.
Full marks in English.
In my opinion,
we normal people
should probably stay away,
lest we get caught in the crossfire.
Sisi.
Let me help you.
No need...
Where should I put it?
Thank you.
Sisi...
Sisi,
look how hard you work every day.
This job doesn't suit you.
It gives you no freedom.
You know what?
I'm now a manager
at the company
run by my dad's friend.
Come to work with me.
I've got your back.
Sisi,
you look so pretty when you smile.
I'm clocking out.
Respected teachers
and fellow students.
Zhi,
is your training fun?
Listen to yourself.
What kind of question is that?
Mom and Dad aren't here.
You can speak normally.
You want to hear normal talk?
It means
you lost your gift.
You got me a gift?
Is this my gift?
This...
Is it for me?
Don't...
Let go, let go.
Isn't it for me?
You let go.
Don't break it.
This is for someone else.
"Someone else"?
You have "someone else"?
Who is it?
A teacher?
No.
Are you having
another sister behind my back?
Who else do you have? Who? Who is it?
Move... Move aside.
Go.
What are you doing?
You have no gift for me,
and you even threw away my lollipop.
Don't eat that.
I've got you something better.
Look.
Chocolate.
Give me that.
What did you just say?
Give it to me.
I was wrong.
What did you just say?
I was wrong. I was wrong.
It's imported chocolate.
We can't even buy this
at our school store.
It's even hard to find in Haizhou,
let alone our school store.
This is all my love for you, sister.
Thank you, Zhi.
Zhi,
why is it so soft?
It looks like it's been squashed.
T-That's just the way it is.
You know,
the more expensive
something is, the weirder it looks.
Are you going to eat it or not?
If not, give it to me.
I will eat it. I will.
My brother bought it for me,
so I'll definitely eat it.
And these.
New Concept English
and the other stuff.
Congratulations to Qi Zhi
on winning
the men's 100-meter championship
at the Sports School's sports meet
this semester.
This certificate is awarded
as encouragement.
A minor championship,
not worth mentioning.
Next,
your brother will become
the National Games champion,
the national champion,
and the Olympic champion.
Okay,
for the sake of the chocolate,
I'll indulge you.
The gold medal
of the men's 100-meter dash
at the 2008 Beijing Olympics goes
to the athlete from China,
Qi Zhi.
Next, please welcome the IOC President,
Qi Shi, to present the award to him.
Done.
Congratulations,
Qi Zhi.
You have won glory
for your country.
Thank you, President. Thank you.
This is the ultimate battle
of human speed, captivating the world.
Let's give a round of applause to Qi Zhi.
This man
from a small town in Northern China
is a young genius
and an unexpected dark horse.
With his own legs,
he created a miracle for China.
Zhi, how come I didn't notice
your amazing gift for bragging
and talking big shamelessly?
I have plenty of amazing gifts.
Take your time to discover them.
Zhi.
Here.
I want to run for class monitor
this semester,
but I just can't write
the speech.
Can you help me write it?
No problem.
Leave
this small matter to me.
Go ahead.
I'll do it right away.
I need time to think.
The famous investment master,
the Sage of Omaha,
Warren Buffett, once said,
"If one day I am gone,
let my wife
put all my..."
"Wife"? Seriously?
Why are you laughing?
Don't laugh.
What is this?
But, but...
No matter what Buffett said,
or whatever an index fund
is like,
choosing a class monitor
is an investment in the future.
Invest a vote in me today,
and I'll return you
a bright future tomorrow.
What nonsense is she talking about?
Seriously?
She's running for it with this?
Bravo!
Applaud!
Good!
-Good!
Thank you, everyone.
Hello, everyone.
I'm not very good with words.
When it comes to sweet-talking,
I probably still need
to learn from Qi Shi.
But if I
become the class monitor,
I will lead the boys in our class
to have more extracurricular activity time
and build up our bodies.
I will also help the girls
with their questions
and improve their grades.
Vice versa.
Any girls
who like playing basketball
are welcome to play sports with us.
And boys are also welcome
to bravely speak out
about their shortcomings.
Let's improve our grades
and grow together.
Thank you, everyone.
-Bravo!
-Good!
[Cao Xin]
[Class Cadre Election]
So annoying!
A Pyrrhic victory.
Let me do it. Let me.
Let me.
Sorrow of Four-eyes,
do you want a game time card
for "Stone Age"?
It's cheap.
Yes, I do.
How much is it?
You're so childish.
You went to play games again
last night, right?
Look at your eye bags.
They're dragging on the floor.
What do you know, nerd?
I play games
to experience different lives.
Cao's the class monitor now, but why did
the homeroom teacher
call you over for a talk?
What did he say?
The homeroom teacher told me that
being a class monitor
would involve many chores
and affect my grades.
He hoped that I
would still play to my own strengths.
He said it was unnecessary
to let these trivial matters
hold me back.
He was specifically comforting you.
The homeroom teacher is quite nice to you.
Special treatment
for first place.
Yeah!
After all, anyone
can run for class monitor.
But what about getting first place?
Not everyone can get first place.
Getting first place
requires real skills.
Real skills.
I heard you, I heard you.
Then, Qi Shi,
our great first-place student,
please pay this month's class fee
and set a good example.
Stop harboring
so many bad intentions
and pretending to be a good student.
I don't have money.
Go back and ask my brother for it.
Okay.
Peelers.
Two yuan, two yuan each.
No need to peel or chop.
Peel with the top, drop from the bottom.
Come on.
Come and take a look.
Do you know who I saw
in the bathhouse 2 days ago?
Who?
Director Zhou!
Director Zhou?
He is now
Deputy General Manager Zhou.
Being a director was a thing of the past.
Peelers.
Come and take a look.
No touching if you're not buying.
How much is this?
This is not for sale.
Why?
Why'd you
buy so many of these things?
Your house is almost like a pool of toads.
The kids like it.
It's fun
and makes nice sounds.
It looks grand at home.
How much is it?
It's been turned into a mining group now.
Do you guys know
where Cao Dongfang ended up?
He was right here, but you didn't ask him.
Now you're asking us who only hear rumors.
Exactly.
If you care about Cao Dongfang so much,
why didn't you ask him just now?
I care about him?
I'm hoping he gets laid off.
You call this caring?
Then you might be waiting forever.
I heard
he was also transferred
to the mining group
as a section chief,
in charge of logistics.
He's got a title, anyway.
Still better off
than us.
He's a section chief now?
Exactly.
The fans you bought
from Hengdong Market
don't have rims.
They look like the ones
fortune tellers use.
Who would buy them?
They sell well.
They're popular with old men.
They look like
Zhuge Liang's feather fan.
Where is that lucky toad?
Did you sell that lucky toad?
You really sold it?
I sold it.
Someone actually wanted
that ugly thing?
It seems that
there's a market for everything.
I'll buy a few more later.
These crafts have a high profit margin.
They make much more money
than selling several boxes of soap.
Forget it, honey.
That thing is hard to sell.
It was sold all by luck.
Besides,
it's heavy and clumsy,
and takes up space.
Our life has just gotten a little better,
and you're getting carried away,
aren't you?
When Qi Shi goes to college,
where will the tuition come from?
Can Qi Zhi look for a job and get married
without some money saved up?
In my opinion,
it's pretty good not working at the mine.
Look,
not to mention anything else,
just
eating on time alone
has actually cured the stomach problems
that I've had for years.
And you don't have insomnia anymore.
When I used to work the night shift
at the mine,
you couldn't sleep all night.
Qi Aihua,
you're really something.
Getting laid off
sounds like a great thing
when you talk about it.
All right, enough.
Don't disturb me
while I'm doing the accounts.
Go away.
Well, Sweetie,
you're pouting so much.
What's wrong?
Your mom made this stir-fried celery
with pork for you.
Isn't it your favorite?
Why didn't you eat it?
Did anyone upset you?
It's a certain someone.
How did he become the class monitor?
He's always one-upping me.
What's so good
about being the class monitor?
It's a waste of time.
Your priority right now
is to focus on your studies, you know?
But I just can't accept it.
They all talk a good game
about everyone being equal.
But when it comes to something like this,
all the benefits go to Cao Xin.
Isn't it just because I look different?
If I looked
like everyone else,
he wouldn't even stand a chance.
Is that what is upsetting you?
Alright, calm down.
Just eat up.
It must be cold now.
Do you want me to heat it up?
No need.
Anyone
can run for class monitor.
Not everyone can get first place.
Getting first place requires real skills.
Cao,
did you go out stealing last night?
Why do you seem
so listless and down lately?
Look at your dark circles.
They're almost bigger than your eyes.
Class,
hand in your test papers
assigned yesterday.
Group 1, Group 2,
what's taking you so long?
Why are you dawdling?
Hurry up.
Group 1, Group 2, what are you doing?
Aren't you usually pretty quick?
What about Group 3?
Cao Xin,
what is this?
You even put a toad on the desk!
Stop laughing!
Quiet!
Go stand in the back.
Class,
now open your textbooks
to page 23.
Today we are going to talk about...
The student by the window,
stop zoning out.
Look at the blackboard.
Look here, here!
Right?
I think it's quite simple, too.
We can try another one later.
What's wrong with you recently?
Is something bothering you?
Then what's with your grades?
In this exam,
you almost fell out of the top 10.
Don't take
this gap of a dozen points lightly.
In the college entrance exam,
a one-point difference
can mean thousands of competitors.
Look at you.
Your grades
dropped drastically this time.
I've been
so worried about you.
Look at Qi Shi.
She always performs stably,
ranking either first or second.
You
really need
to reflect on yourself now.
Try to look for what
you're doing wrong.
If you really can't figure it out,
you can go ask Qi Shi for advice
and ask her how she does it.
Class monitor.
Show me your toad.
Class monitor, class monitor!
Did the homeroom teacher talk to you?
Did he scold you?
Take my advice.
Stop struggling.
Haven't you gotten used to it
after all these years?
Besides,
it's not embarrassing to lose to Qi Shi.
Come here.
What?
Today our class will have
the women's 800-meter fitness test.
Everyone, warm up first.
Stretch a bit.
Qi Shi, what are you doing?
Are you going to run, too?
It's an 800-meter run.
Are you sure you can do it?
I've never done it before.
Let me give it a try.
You don't have to take this test.
Why bother doing it?
We don't want to run, but we have to.
Exactly.
It's exhausting.
Qi Shi,
you should quit it.
It's not worth it if something
goes wrong.
Go rest over there.
It's fine. Just go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Those in the back, keep up.
First row, get ready.
Ready.
Second row,
get ready.
Run faster!
Third row, get ready.
Are you daydreaming?
Here,
wipe your drool.
Get lost.
Cao just can't figure out
why you go to bed
later than him every night,
yet you're still energetic during the day
and even score higher than him.
He wants to know the secret?
Tell Cao Xin to wait
for me under the tree after school.
I'll reveal it myself.
She's making it so mysterious.
Does it look familiar?
It kept you company
when you studied every day.
Actually, I went to bed early.
I left the light on just to motivate you.
What are you doing?
Just you wait.
Are you really that mad? Why?
You just slept a little less.
He really can't take a joke.
So petty!
Mrs. Huo!
Cao Xin.
Are you hungry?
I just bought some pancakes.
No, thanks.
I just want to tell you something.
Haven't you noticed your electricity bill
is higher than usual?
Electricity bill?
Go back and check it out.